PRESENTER 1: All right.
Since we're standing here
in front of the elevator,
let's talk about accessibility.
PRESENTER 2: Those buttons
have Braille notation on them.
PRESENTER 1: And the bell rings
as each floor's number lights
up.
PRESENTER 2: And the
door is really wide,
well, usually it is.
PRESENTER 1: Elevators
are pretty accessible
and that's because accessibility
is important for everyone
whether they
recognize it or not.
PRESENTER 3: Maybe you wear
glasses to improve your vision
or maybe you use
left-handed scissors.
PRESENTER 2: Or maybe that
bum knee makes you walk up
the ramp instead of the stairs.
PRESENTER 1: Or maybe
you're colorblind
and rely on the arrangement
of the lights rather
than the colors.
PRESENTER 3: Whatever your
particular need, the web,
like a good elevator,
should be something
you could navigate with ease.
PRESENTER 1: We're
here to offer insight
into the most common
issues faced by web users.
PRESENTER 2: We want to make
accessible content for all.
PRESENTER 3: If you care
about your content reaching
all learners, you must
care about accessibility.